Hello.
こんにちは
It's super cute.
超かわいいですね
It's more than a rumor.
もう噂以上だね
Is it more than a rumor?
噂以上ですか?
Yes, I heard that you have a really cute girl.
うん、すごいかわいい子がいるって聞いてたんですよ
I wonder if she's an idol or something?
なんかアイドルやってるんでしょうけ?
I'll stop.
やめちゃいます
Are you not doing it now?
今はやってない?
Is it normal now?
今はじゃあ普通に?
student?
学生?
I usually work at a company.
普通に会社にしてます
Hmm, are you working?
んー、働いてるの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫なんですか?
An idol has arrived.
アイドル来たぞって
Didn't you say they all grew up?
みんな生やしたって言ってない?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I thought she was already an idol.
もう もうアイドルだと思ってたからさ
I was so excited.
すごい ドキドキした
I've been holding quite a few events lately.
結構なんか最近もうイベントづくしですけど
Do you have any plans?
予定とかあるんですか?
No.
ないです
Aren't you going on a date?
デートとかしないの?
I want to go on a date.
デートしたい
I want to?
したい?
What are your plans?
予定は?
none.
なし
Do you want to go out to dinner with friends or something?
友達となんか ご飯行くとかそういうこと?
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's the season where I start to miss my human skin quite a bit.
結構人肌恋しくなる季節だしさ
I feel like this person is nice.
この人いいなーみたいな
Isn't there something like that?
そういうのないですか?
why?
なんで?
Don't you have any encounters?
出会いとかないの?
There are no encounters at all.
出会い全然ないですよ
workplace?
職場?
Are you older?
あんま年上とかは?
That's totally true though.
全然ありだけど
Is work work?
仕事は仕事で?
I can't speak to you much.
あんまり声かけられない
That's right.
そうなんだ
Isn't it difficult for everyone to speak out?
みんな声かけづらいんじゃない?
Is it difficult to apply?
かけづらいんですかね
Yeah.
うん
Do you understand?
わかる?
But I can't talk to cute girls.
でも、かわいい子には声かけられないんだよ
There are some types that are easy to talk to.
声かけやすいタイプがいるからさ
Looks like it will be difficult to get through.
かけにくそう
Hey, he's a high level guy.
ちょっとね、レベル高いやつ
I have to ask someone to introduce me.
人遣いで紹介してもらわないと
I need to talk.
話せないと
Christmas.
クリスマス
Would you like some cake?
ケーキでも食べる?
i want to eat.
食べたい
I want to eat it.
食べたいね
You brought so much.
こんなに持ってくるんじゃん
I want her to wear something frilly.
フリフリのやつとか着てもらいたいやん
It definitely suits you.
絶対似合うよね
Good style.
スタイルいいし
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立ってみて
How tall are you?
身長いくつ?
Be
ベ
It's a strike.
スト だね
It seems okay even if the heel is opened.
ヒール開かれても大丈夫そうな
Slowly behind too.
後ろもゆっくり
Just the back.
後ろそのまま
My hair is also quite long.
髪も結構伸ばしてるな
Did you find out?
バレた?
Where are you filming?
どこ撮ってる?
Are you throwing up?
吐いてる?
I'm vomiting.
吐いてますよ
Are you throwing up?
吐いてる?
Wait a minute.
ちょちょちょ
Michihin, I have to check.
みちひん、確認しないと
Do you want to confirm?
確認するの?
Is this a T-bag?
これTバッグなの?
this.
これ
You have a great butt.
すごいお尻してるね
Just a little more.
ちょっとだけもう
It's just my appearance or something.
なんか外見とかあれで
Are you wearing really aggressive underwear?
結構攻めた下着履いてない?
Only behind.
後ろだけ
Only the back?
後ろだけ?
So what's going on before?
じゃあ前はどうなってんの?
forward?
前?
Just flip through it
ちょっとめくってみな
Yo.
よ
Get in the back too.
後 ろにも入って
It's a little risqué.
ちょっとさ、きわどいのがね
This looks like it's going to disappear.
はみ消しそうだなこれね
It's being processed properly.
ちゃんと処理してるんだね
The sides are also very clear.
横もすけすけですね
I think it looks nice.
すけすけがいいなって思う
Do you buy it at a underwear store?
下着屋さんで買うの?
Buy it at a underwear store
下着屋さんで買って
Masu.
ます
That's fine.
結 構じゃいけいけ
It's not okay.
いけいけじゃない
I like underwear.
下着が好きなんだ
I think you'll be surprised.
びっくりしちゃうと思う
Are you attacking?
攻めてますか?
A lot when attacking.
攻めてると、だいぶ
That's right.
そうなんだ
It makes me feel good.
いい感じでくれるのに
Because great relationships are sexy.
すごい仲はセクシーだから
I'll remember it.
思い出てきちゃうね
It's starting to look a little better.
ちょっと上向きになってきちゃったな
This is sexy.
セクシーだねこれね
When I looked inside, it was crossed.
中見たら、 クロスしちゃってんじゃん
It's so erotic.
めっちゃエロいじゃん
It's pure white.
真っ白だね
There's no such thing as sunburn.
日焼けとかもしない
I want to live here.
ここに住みたいもんね
What?
なんだ?
It's transparent.
透けてて
See inside?
中見る?
Because it's already transparent.
もう透けてるからさ
Isn't it going to change?
変わんなくない?
It's not hidden.
隠れてないね
Do you feel like you want to stand out a little bit?
ちょっと目立ちたがりやな感じなんですかね
Like Iriyan.
入林とか
Nearby or big?
近びとか大きいとか
It's feminine.
女性らしいね
Does it rub or rub?
擦れたりとか擦る?
When you were a student, didn't you put stickers on things?
学生の時とかさ、 シール貼ったりとかしなかった?
I didn't put any stickers on it.
シール貼ったりしなかった
Was it okay during learning?
ラーニングの時とかさ、 大丈夫だった?
I did it
したべー
That's it.
って
Are both easy to feel?
ど ちらも感じやすい?
both.
両方
feel?
感じる?
Are you losing your hair?
脱毛してる?
脱毛してるの?
By yourself?
自分で?
remove hair
脱 毛して
Ru?
る?
It's so small.
ち っちゃいね
Do you touch it yourself?
自分で触ったりする?
Have you touched it?
触ったこと?
It won't come out.
出てこないね
be?
ある?
clean?
クリーン?
It's so small.
ち っちゃいね
real?
ほんと?
Are you talking like this?
こんなくちくち言ってるの?
Is it closed?
閉まってる?
閉 ま ってる?
Na
な
To?
に?
Wind Child Ceiling?
風 の子天井?
Wind child ceiling?
風の子天井?
Is it good this morning?
この朝、うまい?
Did you lick it?
ペロペロしてしたの?
Isn't it pan-pan?
パンパンじゃない?
Panpan.
パンパン
That's fine.
いい じゃんか
That's good.
いい じゃん
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Are you taking feelings or something?
気持ちとか取ってる?
I'm taking it.
取ってる
Ah, I'm sitting down.
あ、座ってきた
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
I'm really happy.
すごい嬉しいね
I'm happy.
嬉しいの
Were you surprised?
びっくりしたの?
Get behind me.
後ろについて
Here
ここに
I got it right
当 た
Right?
る でしょ?
It's really low.
めっちゃ下だね
Oh no, I think I'm going to die.
やばい、いっちゃいそう
Is it okay?
いいかな?